chamberofcommerce.com 2018-01-26

# Privacy Policy - ChamberofCommerce.com

EFFECTIVE DATE: 11/1/2009 

1\. Introduction 

ChamberofCommerce.com ("us," "we," or "Company") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website ("the Site"). We created this Website Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review those privacy policies. 

ChamberofCommerce.com uses GeoTrust SSL certificates throughout its site to insure the security and privacy of personal and financial information submitted. GeoTrust is the world's second largest digital certificate provider, and a leader in a wide variety of Identity and Trust services. More than 100,000 customers in over 150 countries use GeoTrust products to secure online transactions, confirm and protect identities, and operate fully managed trusted environments for conducting business over the Internet. 

2\. Information Collection Practices 

_2.1 Types of Information Collected_

_2.1.1 Traffic Data Collected_  
We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain names; (3) domain servers; (4) access times; (5) types of computers accessing the Site; and (6) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We may also use "cookies" to customize content specific to your interests and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to your computer. Using cookies can enhance your experience of the Site. However, you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize the interactive features of the Site. 

_2.1.2 Personal and Business Information Collected_  
In order for you to access certain services such as creating a user profile, uploading videos, posting messages in our forums, reviewing businesses, entering contests, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists that we offer via the Site, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address) and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and occupation). 

_2.1.3 Rights of Information_  
This information is proprietary to Acxiom Corporation and is protected under U.S. copyright law and international treaty provisions. This information is licensed for your personal or professional use and may not be resold or provided to others.  You may not distribute, sell, rent, sublicense, or lease such information, in whole or in part to any third party; and you will not make such Acxiom information available in whole or in part to any other user in any networked or time-sharing environment, or transfer the information in whole or in part to any computer other than the PC used to access this information. _2.2 Uses of Information Collected_

_2.2.1 Company Use of Information_  
We may use your Personal Information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Site. When you register with ChamberofCommerce.com you agree to receive email communications from ChamberofCommerce.com about related news, information, products and services. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your Personal Information and certain Traffic Data to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. 

_2.2.2 Sharing of Personal Information_  
Except as explained herein, we do not share your Personal Information with third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We only disclose your Personal Information to our service providers who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, monitoring, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. Those service providers have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Company. 

We reserve the right to share or transfer your Personal Information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Company or substantially all of Company's assets. 

_2.2.3 User Choice Regarding Collection of Personal Information_  
You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. 

_2.2.4 Third party advertising_  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect data when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

3\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information 

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser. 

_.1 User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information_   
We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may, visit your personal profile. Through your personal profile you may review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected. 

_3.2 Lost or Stolen Information_  
You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that user name or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

_3.3 Public Information_  
The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may also make chat rooms, video uploading, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information. 

4\. Contacting Us and Policy Updates

_4.1 User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information_  
If you have any questions about this Policy, our privacy practices related to this Site, or if you would like us to remove your information from our database please feel free to contact us at [unsubscribe@ChamberofCommerce.com](mailto:unsubscribe@chamberofcommerce.com). 

_4.2 Updates to this Privacy Policy_  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
